(
"ai_sub_version": "1.9.2",
"subtitles_prompt_version": 2,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": "gemini-cli:gemini-3-flash-preview",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600
)
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": true,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"encoder": "libx264"
)
),
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"subtitles": 8
),
"retry": (
"run": 3,
"max": 9,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": false,
"scrub": true
)
SakuraMiko 3rd Anniversary LIVE Shine more!!!
マイネームイズエリート☆
作詞・作曲：キノシタ
My Name is Elite☆
Lyrics/Composition: Kinoshita
わんつーで参拝！
One, two, let's pray!
みこみこみこー（いぇーい！）
Miko-miko-miko! (Yay!)
ついに来たよ お待たせ！
I'm finally here, thanks for waiting!
待ちに待った うへへへ
I've waited so long! Uhehehe
電脳の世界からやってきた
I came from the cyber world
ウザカワ系バーチャル巫女アイドル！
An annoyingly cute virtual shrine maiden idol!
わたしはそう エリート！ (エリート？)
That's right, I'm Elite! (Elite?)
なんてったって エリート！ (えっへん！)
No matter what, I'm Elite! (Ahem!)
エリート巫女 エリートアイドル
Elite shrine maiden, elite idol
そんなの両方に決まってるじゃん
Of course I'm both!
いじわるも泣き虫もカミサマも！？
Meanies, crybabies, and gods too!?
崇めたら巫女パワーで
If you worship me, with shrine maiden power...
幸せわけてあげてもいいんだよ？
...I might just share some happiness with you.
(みこちゃんはー？ エリートです！)
(What is Miko-chan? I'm elite!)
みこみこみこで にゃっふーにゃ
Miko-miko-miko, nya-hoo-nya
さくらひらり さくらみこ（みこ！みこ！）
Cherry blossoms fluttering, Sakura Miko (Miko! Miko!)
みこみこみこで むにゃむにゃにゃ
Miko-miko-miko, munya-munya-nya
明日から本気だす（セリフ：エリートですから！）
I'll start trying hard tomorrow (Dialogue: Because I'm elite!)
みこみこみこで にゃっふーにゃ
Miko-miko-miko, nya-hoo-nya
全肯定はほどにゃにゃにゃ（たぶん！）
Unconditional praise is just right (Probably!)
幸せの太鼓 ポンポコリンリンリン（ポンポン！）
Drums of happiness, ponpoko-rin-rin-rin (Pon-pon!)
みんな笑顔になあれ
Everyone, let's smile!
わんつーで参拝！
One, two, let's pray!
みこみこみこー（いぇーい！）
Miko-miko-miko! (Yay!)
はい！ はい！ はい！ はい！
Hi! Hi! Hi! Hi!
ちょっとだけ休憩タイム
Just a little break time
マイペースだけど許してね！
I go at my own pace, but forgive me!
実はこれも修行のうちです
Actually, this is also part of my training
そんなわけはなくなくない…
It's not like that, not not...
わたしはそう エリート！ (エリート？)
That's right, I'm Elite! (Elite?)
嘘じゃないよ エリート！ (えっへん！)
It's not a lie, I'm Elite! (Ahem!)
エリート巫女 エリートアイドル
Elite shrine maiden, elite idol
今日もがんがんがんばっていきましょう！
Let's do our very best today too!
サクラ模様 曇り色 雨の日も！？
Cherry blossom patterns, cloudy skies, even on rainy days!?
問題ない！巫女パワーで
No problem! With shrine maiden power...
それ天晴れパレード！騒いじゃおうよ！
That's a splendid parade! Let's get loud!
(チャンネル登録してくれやあ！)
(Please subscribe to the channel!)
みこみこみこで にゃっふーにゃ
Miko-miko-miko, nya-hoo-nya
さくらひらり さくらみこ（みこ！みこ！）
Cherry blossoms fluttering, Sakura Miko (Miko! Miko!)
みこみこみこで むにゃむにゃにゃ
Miko-miko-miko, munya-munya-nya
たいやきめでたいやき（セリフ：Thank you！）
Taiyaki, celebratory taiyaki (Dialogue: Thank you!)
カミサマもほににゃににゃににゃ たぶん！
God too is mumbling something, probably!
元気の呪文 みこ舞舞！ (しゃんしゃん！)
Energy spell, Miko-Maimai! (Shan shan!)
みんな笑顔になあれ！
Everyone, put on a smile!
わんつー あ！間違えたぁー！
One, two... Ah! I messed up!
にゃっはろー！みんな楽しんでる？？
Nyahallo! Is everyone having fun??
ここからはスーパーみこみこタイム！
From here on, it's Super Miko-Miko Time!
ぜーったいに遅れずについてきてね？！
Make sure you don't fall behind, okay?!
みんなで一緒にお手を拝借！はい！
Everyone, clap along with me! Go!
みーこ！みーこ！ (みーこ！みーこ！)
Miko! Miko! (Miko! Miko!)
みこはエリート！ (みこはエリート！)
Miko is an elite! (Miko is an elite!)
E-L-I-T-E! (E-L-I-T-E!)
エリート！エリート！イェーー！！
Elite! Elite! Yay!!
ラストにもう一回張り切って行くよーっ！
Let's give it our all for the home stretch!
みこみこみこみこde
Miko-miko-miko-miko de
ほににゃににゃににゃ たぶん ごろごろごろにゃっぺ (しゃんしゃん！)
Mumbling something, probably, rolling around (Shan shan!)
みこみこみこみこde
Miko-miko-miko-miko de
ミョーはひょこみょっぴー チャームポイントですから！ (みょん！)
The way I hop is my charm point! (Myon!)
みこみこみこみこde
Miko-miko-miko-miko de
ほににゃににゃににゃ たぶん
Mumbling something, probably
ちをしのでごこ ぽんぽんぽん！ (ぽんぽん！)
In high spirits, pop-pop-pop! (Pop-pop!)
みんな笑顔になあれ！
Everyone, put on a smile!
わんつーでんぱ！ みこみこみこイェイ！
One, two, den-pah! Miko-miko-miko-yay!
最後に右参拝！ みこみこみこイェイ☆
Last clap! Miko-miko-miko-yay☆
はい！ということで！
Alright! So!
にゃっはろー！
Nyahallo!
ホロライブ所属の、エリートみこアイドル、
I'm the elite Miko idol of Hololive,
さくらみこです！
Sakura Miko!
ということで、今回は、みこの3周年、
So, thank you all for coming to Miko's 3rd Anniversary,
3rd Anniversaryのライブに来てくれてどうもありがとうございます！
3rd Anniversary LIVE! Thank you so much!
イェーイ！みんな見てる？
Yay! Is everyone watching?
ということでね、今回のライブのタイトルを、
So, for this live show's title...
「Shine more!!!」というタイトルに決めさせていただきました！イェーイ！
I've decided on the title "Shine more!!!" Yay!
まね、この装飾にもありますように、
Well, as you can see from these decorations,
今回は夏をテーマにしたライブとなっております。
this live's theme is summer.
そしてもっと輝くみこちゃんは、
And to shine even brighter, Mikocchi...
4周年目も、もっと輝いていくぞ！ということで。
will shine even more in her fourth year!
今回ね、ライブを頑張っていきたいと思いますので、
I'm going to give it my best for this live,
皆さん最後まで絶対見よな！
so please make sure to watch until the very end!
よろしくお願いします！
Thank you very much!
ということで、本日はね、ゲスト、
And today, I have a guest...
ゲスト呼んでいるんですよ！やったー！
I've invited a guest! Hooray!
ということで、ゲストを呼んでいこうかな。
So, shall I call my guest?
どうぞー！
Come on out!
全力☆summer!
Zenkuryoku☆summer!
今日もいい天気だ
The weather's great again today!
私のためだけ地球はグルグル回ります
The Earth spins around just for me!
よっこらしょいしょい 勉強なんてね
Heave-ho! I'm an expert at...
見て見ぬふりが得意です
pretending I didn't see any studies!
それより海とか行きたいサマーだ！
More than that, it's a summer for the beach!
アイアイアイサー I want you!
Aye-aye-sir, I want you!
愛してココナッツ 感じて灼熱
Love these coconuts, feel the heat...
ラブミーテンダーかき氷
Love me tender, shaved ice!
あっけらかん (ぞとも言う)
Indifferent (or rather, the same).
天才とは紙一重
Genius and madness are but a paper's width apart.
海行きたい (だがしかし)
I want to go to the ocean, however...
日焼けは恐ろしや…
Sunburn is terrifying...
がっとばせ夏が来た！
Knock it out of the park, summer has come!
期待のルーキー夏休み？！
The long-awaited rookie, summer vacation?!
恋い焦がれたら
If you're head over heels...
全力アピール
full-power appeal!
何様？お疲れサマー
What's with this "Otsukaresummer"?
カッコつけない魅惑のラブストーリー
A charming, unpretentious love story!
ダーリン I love you (ポア ポア)
Darling, I love you (Mwah, mwah!)
聖人君子も あなたも私も
Saints, you, and me...
結局つまりは人間です
after all, we're all just human!
早口言葉だ！ バナナにバナナがバナナで
It's a tongue twister! Banana, banana...
バナナのバナナバナナ
Banana, banana, banana, banana, banana!
それよりキャンプに行きたいサマーだ！
More than that, it's a summer for camping!
BBQでバーベキュー
BBQ at a barbecue!
それから夜には花火をしようよ
And then, let's set off fireworks at night...
二人きりだけのアイランド
an island just for the two of us!
あっけらかん (ぞとも言う)
Indifferent (or rather, the same).
天才とは紙一重
Genius and madness are but a paper's width apart.
肉食べたい (だがしかし)
I want to eat meat, however...
いわゆる炭火焼き…
a so-called charcoal grill...
がっとばせ夏が来た！
Knock it out of the park, summer has come!
地球のテンション急上昇！
The Earth's tension is soaring!
待ち焦がれたら
If you're long-awaiting it...
全力バケーション
full-power vacation!
Full power vacation
何様？おつかれサマー
Who are you? Good job this summer
ちょっと待って とろけちゃいそうよ
Wait a minute, I'm about to melt
ダーリン I need you
Darling I need you
酸いも甘いもかぎ分けず
Without distinguishing between sour and sweet
甘いだけです青二才
It's just sweet, you greenhorn
それよいよい
Sore yoiyoi
あれよいよい
Are yoiyoi
天の川
Milky Way
ガラの空きっ端
The edge of an empty sky
かっとばせ夏が来た
Let's go, summer is here
期待のルーキー 夏休み？
The expected rookie, summer vacation?
追いすがれたら 全力アピール
If I'm chased, I'll give it my all
何様？おつかれサマー
Who are you? Good job this summer
カッコつけない魅惑のラブストーリー
An uncool, enchanting love story
ダーリン I love you
Darling I love you
かっとばせ夏が来た
Let's go, summer is here
地球のテンション 急上昇
The Earth's tension is rising rapidly
待ち焦がれるほど
So much that I've been waiting for it
全力バケーション
Full power vacation
何様？おつかれサマー
Who are you? Good job this summer
ちょっと待って とろけちゃいそうよ
Wait a minute, I'm about to melt
ダーリン I need you
Darling I need you
(ホアホア)
(Hoa hoa)
そろそろこの曲終わりになるから 空前絶後のよろしくね
This song is about to end, so give me an unprecedented 'yoroshiku'
センチメンタル鋼のメンタル それでも明日は筋肉痛
Sentimental steel heart, but tomorrow I'll have muscle pain
逆のパンツ履いていくわ 私をしっかり信じてね
I'll wear my underwear inside out, believe in me
世界で一番 こんなに楽しい夏の日をありがとう
Thank you for the most fun summer day in the world
おつかれサマー
Good job this summer
はい、ということで！
Yes, and so!
スバルに来てもらいました！
We have Subaru here!
ちゅばー！
Chuba!
お邪魔します！
Excuse me for interrupting!
みこちありがとう！
Mikochi, thank you!
３周年おめでとう！
Happy 3rd anniversary!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
おめでたい、おめでたい。
Congrats, congrats.
今回はね、ちょっと「夏」って感じのライブにしたかったので、スバルちゃんかなと思いましてね。
This time, I wanted a live with a "summer" feel, so I thought of Subaru-chan.
あとあんまり一緒に、3Dとかでやったことないから、意外と。
And we haven't really done much together in 3D, surprisingly.
そうそう、スバルだって、初めてこうやってメンバーのライブにゲストで出たから、結構緊張しちゃったよ。
Right, right. Even for Subaru, this is the first time I've been a guest on a member's live, so I was pretty nervous.
やったー！一番乗り！
Yay! First one!
おめでとう、本当に。
Congratulations, really.
ありがとう。
Thank you.
はい、ということで、
So, with that said,
まだね、ゲストがいますので、
We still have more guests,
なんて！？
What!?
呼んでいこうかなと思います！
I'm going to call them out!
おお！
Oh!
次は、ころね！
Next is, Korone!
ころねー！
Korone!
お邪魔しますよ〜！
I'm coming in!
やあ、スバルちゃん、いってくーで。
Hey, Subaru-chan, I'm going in.
頑張ってね！
Good luck!
はい！
Okay!
はい、ということで、みころね、歌います！
So, Mikorone will sing!
聞いてください！
Please listen!
ニッポン笑顔百景！
Nippon Egao Hyakkei!
ニッポン笑顔百景
Nippon Egao Hyakkei
よぉ〜！
Yo~!
じゅげむ じゅげむ 五劫のすりきれ
Jugemu Jugemu Goko no Surikire
海砂利水魚の 水行末 雲来末 風来末
Kaijarisuigyo no Suigyomatsu Unraimatsu Furaimatsu
食う寝る処に住む処 やぶら小路の藪柑子
A place to eat, sleep, and live; Yaburakoji's Yabukoji
パイポパイポ パイポのシューリンガン
Paipopaipo Paipo's Shuringan
シューリンガンのグーリンダイ
Shuringan's Gurindai
グーリンダイのポンポコピーの
Gurindai's Ponpokopi's
ポンポコナの長久命の長助
Ponpokona's Chokyumei's Chosuke
ちょいとお時間いただきます
I'll take a little of your time
ご静聴ください
Please listen carefully
整いました！
I'm ready!
笑うこととかけまして
Comparing laughter...
お祭り野郎とときます
...to a festival guy
そのこころは？
And the punchline is?
どちらもハッピ(法被)になるでしょう
Both will become 'happi' (happy/festival coat)!
お後がよろしいようで
The time is right for the next act
笑うおう 笑おう さぁ笑いましょう
Let's laugh, let's laugh, let's laugh together
こんな時代こそ笑いましょう
In times like these, let's laugh
笑おう(ソイヤ ソイヤ)
Let's laugh (Soiya Soiya)
泣いたら負けだぜ
If you cry, you lose
やけくそ笑いましょう
Let's laugh desperately
波乱万丈 酸いも甘いも
Ups and downs, through thick and thin
乗り越えた
We've overcome it all
あっぱれ日本人
Wonderful Japanese people
笑おう！
Let's laugh!
どんな時でも
No matter when
なにクソ 笑いましょう
With a 'nani kuso' spirit, let's laugh
グワッハッハ！
Gwahahha!
ニョッホッホ！
Nyohohho!
空気なんて読まずに笑っとけ
Don't read the room, just laugh
笑顔！ 笑顔！
Smile! Smile!
笑う門には福来たる！
Fortune comes to those who smile!
皆様 今日はようこそおいでいただきました
Everyone, welcome and thank you for coming today
皆様、今日はようこそおいでいただきました。
Welcome, everyone, and thank you for coming today.
ここで一席！！
And now, a performance!!
ねずみの娘がお嫁に行って、じきに帰ってきたんで、
A mouse's daughter got married and came home soon after,
ねずみのおかあさんが、大変怒って、
so the mouse mother was very angry,
「あんな、いいところへ、おまえ嫁いで、
"You married into such a good place,
誰が嫌で、出てきたんだい？」
who did you dislike so much that you left?"
「いいえ、だーれも嫌じゃないんですけれど、
"No, I didn't dislike anyone, but
ご隠居さんがやさしいんで、嫌なの。」
the retired master was so kind that I disliked it."
「やさしいんなら結構じゃあないかえ。」
"If he's kind, isn't that wonderful?"
「でも、ねこなで声ですもの。」
"But, he speaks in a cat-like voice."
ニャー！
Meow!
忙しさに身を任せて
Giving myself over to the busyness
消えていくなんて べらんめえ！
Vanishing away? Nonsense!
笑おう 笑おう 笑えなくても
Let's laugh, let's laugh, even if we can't
笑うしかないでしょ 笑いましょう
We have to laugh, so let's laugh
もう（ソイヤ ソイヤ）
Come on now (Soiya soiya)
口上げて ひたむきに笑いましょう
Open your mouth and laugh wholeheartedly
お見事 大盛況さぁ
Splendid, a great success
クリアして 現代 日本人 笑おう
Getting through it, modern Japanese, let's laugh
未来永劫 グハハと笑いましょう
For all eternity, let's laugh out loud
小娘のたわごと と切り捨てないで
Don't dismiss it as a young girl's nonsense
しかめつら なんか変な顔
Frowning is such a strange face
笑顔を見たいから
I want to see your smile
笑おう 笑おう さぁ 笑いましょう
Let's laugh, let's laugh, come on, let's laugh
こんな時代こそ 笑いましょう
Especially in times like these, let's laugh
笑おう（ソイヤ ソイヤ）
Let's laugh (Soiya soiya)
泣いたら負け やけくそ笑いましょう
If you cry, you lose, let's laugh desperately
腹八分 粋も甘いも
Eighty percent full, both refined and sweet
乗り越えた あっぱれ 日本人 笑おう
We overcame it, bravo Japanese, let's laugh
どんな時でも なにくそ 笑いましょう
No matter when, let's laugh with determination
ひたすら 笑いましょう
Let's laugh earnestly
ぐはっはっは（ぐはっはっは）
Guhahaha (Guhahaha)
にょほほ（にょほほ） 勇気なんてよも末に笑い飛ばせ
Nyohoho (Nyohoho) Laugh away your courage at the end
笑顔（笑顔） 笑顔（笑顔）
Smile (Smile), Smile (Smile)
笑う門には福来る！
Fortune comes to those who smile!
はい、ということでー！
Yes, and so!
イェーイ！ころさーん！
Yay! Koro-san!
ころさん、おめでとう！
Koro-san, congratulations!
すごい！一緒に歌えてすごい嬉しい！あ、ありがとう。
Amazing! I'm so happy we could sing together! Oh, thank you.
そうなんだよ！みっころねで、3Dで。
That's right! Miccorone, in 3D.
初めてなの！
It's the first time!
そうなんです、イェーイ！
That's right, yay!
みっころね初3D！
Miccorone's first 3D!
ありがとう、来てくれて。もうすごい嬉しい。駆けつけちゃった。
Thank you for coming. I'm so happy. I just rushed here.
ね、この曲ね、みっころねっぽいかなと思って選ばせてもらったんだ。
You know, I chose this song because I thought it was very Miccorone-like.
ころねもこの曲大好きで！
Korone also loves this song!
そう、みこみこと一緒に歌いたいなと思ってたから、今回歌えて嬉しかった！
Yes, I wanted to sing it with Mikomiko, so I was really happy to sing it!
やったー！みこもね、この曲はね、ころねの歌枠で知ったんだよ。
Yay! Miko too, I found out about this song through Korone's singing stream.
え、そうなの！？
Oh, really!?
そうなの！イェーイ！
Yes! Yay!
嬉しい！
I'm happy!
ということで、今回、もう一人呼びたいかなって思います。
So, I'd like to call one more person this time.
スバルー！
Subaru!
いる？
Are you here?
こえーよ！
You're scary!
イェーイ！
Yay!
確かに初めてだもんね、このメンツ。
It certainly is the first time for this group.
なんでスバルみっころねのところに呼んでもらえたんだ、嬉しい！
Why was Subaru called to join Miccorone? I'm so happy!
スバ、スバ、スバ！よろしくお願いします！
Suba, suba, suba! Nice to meet you!
せっかくだから、ちょっと撮影をしたいなと思うんですけどいいですか？
Since we're here, I'd like to take some photos, is that okay?
やったー！やりたいやりたい。
Yay! I want to, I want to.
じゃあちょっと3人で。みこ真ん中でいい？
Then, the three of us. Miko, is it okay if you're in the middle?
真ん中はもちろん、もちろん！
The middle? Of course, of course!
どんなポーズがいいの？
What kind of pose should we do?
なんかさ、カメラ寄ってもらって。あ、いいじゃん！
Let's have the camera move closer. Oh, that's good!
おにゃー！イェーイ！
Onyaa! Yay!
すぐ殴るじゃん！カツアゲですよカツアゲ。やべーわ。
You start punching right away! This is extortion. This is bad.
はい、会場のみんなとも撮りたいなと思って！
Yes, I also want to take photos with everyone in the venue!
あっちあっち！カメラ回ってもらって。
That way! Have the camera turn around.
すげー！
Amazing!
え、しゃがんで撮る？座って撮るやつ、よくあるやつ。
Should we crouch and take it? The sitting one, the usual kind.
イェーイ！
Yay!
わーエモいなー。嬉しい！
Wow, that's emotional. I'm happy!
めっちゃいい。ライブだライブ！
So good. It's a live concert!
ピースピース！
Peace, peace!
商売商売商売商売。
Business business business business.
たいやきたいやきたいやきたいやき。
Taiyaki taiyaki taiyaki taiyaki.
あと何ある？
What else is there?
えーどうしようかな。じゃあスバちゃんと、ハートマーク作ろうかな。
Hmm, what to do. Then, I'll make a heart mark with Suba-chan.
いいよ！
Okay!
やれやれ！
Go for it!
その中にみこみこみこ...
And in the middle, Miko-Miko-Miko...
前前！
Front! Front!
後ろ後ろ！
Back! Back!
いくぞ！
Here we go!
あ、なんかサンドの気持ちになる。いい感じじゃん。やだーありがとう！
Ah, I feel like the filling of a sandwich. This feels nice. No way, thank you!
え、かわいい！めっちゃかわいい！
Eh, cute! So cute!
えー、二人とも本当に来てくれてありがとうね。こちらこそありがとうございました。
Both of you, thank you so much for coming. The pleasure was all ours.
じゃあみこ、このあとも頑張るんだよ。
Well Miko, keep working hard for the rest of the show.
頑張ってね！お水飲んでね。しっかり頑張ってね。頑張ります！
Good luck! Drink some water. Do your best! I will!
ありがとうございます！ということで、みことお友、みこずまでした！
Thank you! And so, we were Miko and Friends, Mikozuma!
緊急ミッション サプライズをしろ
Emergency Mission: Pull off a surprise
えっ！？クエスト！？なんかクエストが発生している！
Eh!? A quest!? Some kind of quest has been triggered!
何だ？何が起こった？何が起こった？
What is it? What happened? What happened?
これはヤバい気配がします！クエスト、クエストじゃん！
I'm getting a bad feeling about this! It's a quest!
み、みこっち、クエストだって！
M-Miko-chi, it's a quest!
何これ！何だこれ！何これ！？いいですか？ちょっと開けても。
What is this? What on earth? What is it!? Can I open it?
リハーサルでも何も言わなかったじゃない！
You didn't say anything about this in rehearsal!
じゃーん！すごい！本物じゃんこれ！ちょっと説明してもらっていいですか？
Ta-da! Wow! This is the real deal! Can you explain what's going on?
みこピーの皆さんがですね、みこっちのために...
The Miko-p's got this for you, Miko-chi...
えー、このね、ゲームの... GTAのですね、開発者さんのサインをもらってきてもらったんです！
They managed to get autographs from the GTA developers!
えー！ヤバい！うそでしょ！？すごーい！みんな見て後ろの写真！
Eh! No way! Are you serious!? Amazing! Everyone, look at the photos behind us!
えー！ヤバい！うそー！センキュー！センキュー！I love you GTA!
Eh! No way! No way! Thank you! Thank you! I love you GTA!
本当だー！ヤバい！本物だこれ！こっちもいっぱいあるよ。
It's true! Wow! These are real! There's a lot over here too.
えー！そんなの持ってきていいの？ほら三つある、三つ！
Eh! Is it okay to bring all these? Look, there are three of them!
すごい！ヤバいじゃんこれ！みこっち今の気持ちをカメラにどうぞ。
Amazing! This is incredible! Miko-chi, tell the camera how you feel.
GTA I love you! 本当にありがとう！おめでとうおめでとう！
GTA I love you! Thank you so much! Congratulations!
あれ？知らなかったよね、みこみこは。
Wait, you really didn't know, did you?
マジで知らなかった。ガチびびった！ガチでびびった！
I really had no idea. I'm literally shaking! Literally!
大事にね！大事に。でもね、みこみこほら、まだ歌があるからさ。
Keep them safe! But Miko, you still have more songs to sing.
一旦これ回収させてもらって。ヤダー！ダメ、みこみこ。集中して。
We'll take these for now. No way! Yes, Miko, you need to focus.
店長に預けて... ヤバい！
Leave them with the manager... This is crazy!
じゃあみこっち頑張ってね！頑張るんだよ！ありがとう！
Alright Miko-chi, good luck! You can do it! Thank you!
えー、マジで。はぁー... びっくりしたんですけど。
Seriously. Haa... I was so surprised.
ということでね、このあとも頑張っていきたいと思いまーす。センキュー！
So, I'm going to keep doing my best. Thank you!
えっ、ちょっとヤバい。動悸がヤバい。
Wait, this is bad. My heart is racing.
adrenaline!!! 作詞・作曲：中野領太 (onetrap)
adrenaline!!! Lyrics & Composition: Ryota Nakano (onetrap)
単純な言葉　重ねてゆく
Stacking up simple words
もっと心は素直で
The heart should be more honest
なんでもないような　その笑顔が
That seemingly ordinary smile
明日を照らす光に
Will become the light that lights up tomorrow
ずっと気づいていたんだって
I've always noticed it
この手に抱えていたんだって
I've been holding it in my hands
弾けた声に
In that bursting voice
零した答えが今
The answer I let slip is now
今　そっと　きっと　願いこめた
Now, surely and gently, filled with a wish
ずっとまわる　まわる　夢の中で
Spinning, spinning in a dream forever
繰り返し　君と踊った
Over and over, I danced with you
揺れる景色　道は続く
Swaying scenery, the road continues
通り過ぎる　風に吹かれ
Blown by the passing wind
何度も越えて行けるから　境界線
I can cross the boundary line again and again
今　かき分けて　手を伸ばした
Now, pushing through, I reached out my hand
涙は今　浮かぶ空に預けて
I'll leave my tears in the floating sky
走り出すの
And start running
涙は今　浮かぶ空に預けて　走り出すの
Now, leave your tears to the floating sky and start running.
並んで　見つけた
Standing side by side, I found it.
輝く光を手に
With the shining light in my hands.
ふー！
Fu!
問題はいつも自分次第
The problem is always up to you.
さぁ　未来を選んで
Now, choose your future.
こんがらがった糸ほどいたら
Once you untangle the knotted threads...
思いのまま　進もう
...let's move forward as your heart desires.
毎日冒険なんだって
Every day is an adventure.
奇跡は無限大なんだって
Miracles are infinite.
高鳴る　想い
Thumping feelings...
羅針盤のように　今
...like a compass, now...
そっと　きっと　導いてく
...will surely, gently guide you.
そうだ！めぐるめぐる波に乗っかって
That's right! Ride the cycling waves...
どこまでも先　君と笑った
...I laughed with you all the way ahead.
予想外は　想定内
The unexpected is within expectations.
間違いや　失敗も楽しんで
Enjoy your mistakes and failures too.
一歩踏み出したら見えた可能性
The possibilities I saw when I took a step forward.
行き止まりの先交わして
Dodge what lies beyond the dead end...
まだ知らない　世界　君と一緒なら
...if I'm with you in this unknown world...
怖くないよ
...I'm not afraid.
わくわくしている
I'm getting excited.
今が一番大好き
I love "now" the most.
ハイ！ハイ！ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
ゆっくり (ゆっくり)
Slowly (slowly).
焦らない (焦らない)
Don't rush (don't rush).
自分の (自分の)
At your own (your own)...
歩幅でいこう
...pace, let's go.
大丈夫 (大丈夫)
It's okay (it's okay).
心配ない (心配ない)
No need to worry (no need to worry).
描いたもの　全部叶えるよ
Everything you've drawn, I'll make it all come true.
ずっと　まわる　まわる　夢の中で
Constantly spinning, spinning in a dream...
繰り返し君と歌った
...I sang with you over and over again.
いつか君と約束した
The promise I made with you someday...
願いの架け橋を渡って
...crossing the bridge of wishes.
何度も　超えていけるから　限界を
Because we can overcome our limits again and again.
霧かき分け手を伸ばした
Pushing through the fog, I reached out my hand.
涙は今　浮かぶ空に預けて
Now, leave your tears to the floating sky...
走り出すの
...and start running.
並んで　見つけた　輝く光を手に
Standing side by side, I found the shining light in my hands.
わくわくしている
I'm getting excited.
今が一番大好き
I love "now" the most.
ふー！
Fu!
はい、ということで
Yes, so...
どうですか？見て見て見て見て見て見て！
How do I look? Look, look, look, look, look, look!
えーただいまですね、みこちゃんコラボカフェを、あの開催しておりまして
Um, right now, I'm holding a Miko-chan collaboration cafe...
エリートカフェって言うんですけど
...it's called "Elite Cafe."
その時のね、こうなんて言うのかな、店長の証というか
It's like, how should I put it, a symbol of being the manager...
そんな感じで、カチューシャをね、つけてもらいました！
...so I've put on this headpiece!
どう？可愛い？
How is it? Is it cute?
イェーイ！
Yay!
はい！ということで
Yes! So...
あの現在、あ、え？
Um, currently... oh, what?
何？何何何何？
What? What what what what?
何の、え何？
What... eh, what?
ちょっと聞いてないんですけど。は？
Wait, I haven't heard about this. Huh?
ビデオメッセージが届いています
A video message has arrived.
ビデオメッセージが届いてます。え？
A video message has arrived. Eh?
え、何これ？
Eh, what's this?
うっ
Ugh...
おま、何で！
You... why?!
何で来てんの、お前！ちょっと！
Why are you here?! Wait!
スタッフさん流れてますけど！え？
Staff, it's playing! Eh?
おい！お前！
Hey! You!
にゃっはろー！
Nyahharo!
にゃっはろーじゃないよ！
Don't "Nyahharo" me!
みんな、楽しんでるかー？
Everyone, are you having fun?
ちょっとみんな違うんですよ！ちょっと待ってください！
Wait, everyone, it's not like that! Please wait!
なんと、みこは
Believe it or not, Miko...
こっちの世界でも、活動ができるように
...in order to be active in this world too...
新しい姿を、手に入れたんだよね
...got a new appearance!
いや、あの、そう、あの
No, well, yes, um...
巫女の分身ってわけだね。
It's Miko's alter ego, right?
ちょっと待てよお前！なんで勝手にやってんの！
Wait a second, you! Why are you doing that on your own!
姿を...
The appearance...
姿をじゃねえお前！
It's not about the appearance, you!
可愛い。まあ、巫女が元だからね、可愛いは当たり前なんだけど。
Cute. Well, since I'm the original, it's natural for it to be cute.
いや、違う、あのね、巫女違うの。これはね、勝手に分裂をし始めたというか。
No, wait, it's different. This thing started splitting on its own.
いきなり出てきたというか、巫女は全然知らないんですよ、こいつなんて。
It suddenly appeared, I don't know this guy at all!
あ！ちょっと！何風に！あや！
Ah! Wait! What is this wind! Ouch!
あー！すごい飛んでる！すごい飛んでる！
Ah! It's flying so much! It's flying so much!
待って！なんかおかしい！ちょっと待って！うああああああ！
Wait! Something's wrong! Hold on! Aaaaaah!
やだー！
Nooo!
はぁ。いやぁ、あの。
Phew. Well, uh.
いや、そうなんですね。ちょっと、まあみんなに言うのは遅れたんですけど。
Yeah, so... well, I was a bit late telling everyone.
結構前から、なんか分裂しそうだなっていう予感はありまして、なんかこういう風になりました。
I had a feeling for a while that I might split, and it turned out like this.
あのね、いや違うんだよ。なんか今日もね、なんか勝手にあいつがさ、なんか秋葉原とか歩いてましたけどね。巫女は全く知らなかったんだよ。
No, really. Even today, that guy was walking around Akihabara on his own. I had no idea.
なんかみんなにはもう知られてたみたいですけど。はい。
It seems everyone already knew, though. Yes.
まあ、そんな感じで、なんか巫女の、まあ分身というか、凶暴なところを8割固めたものみたいなやつが。
So, it's like my alter ego, or rather, a being composed of 80% of my ferocity.
ちょっと、まあ今後ね、まあ仕方ねえから共に活動していくのかなって思います。まあどういう形になるかわかりませんけれども。
So I guess we'll be active together from now on since I have no choice. I don't know what form that will take, though.
まあ、みこだよ、みこだよとか呼ばれてたけど。呼び方は自由にしてやってください。
People were calling it "Miko-dai" or whatever, but feel free to call it what you want.
巫女の凶暴なところを80%固めたようなやつなんで、今後ともどうぞ、まあ、お手柔らかによろしくお願いいたします。
Since it's 80% of my ferocious side, please be gentle with it from now on.
ということで、もう勝手にさ、ちょっと始めやがったからさ、ライブのテンポが崩れたじゃねえか。
Anyway, it just started on its own, so the live's tempo got messed up!
ということで、まあ今後もね、このあともどんどんライブやっていくので、みんな最後まで見てくれよな。
So we'll keep the live going, please watch until the end!
巫女はこのあとね、ちょっと可愛い衣装にお着替えしてきたいなと思います。
I'm going to go change into a cute outfit now.
それでは！お着替え行ってきまーす！
Well then! I'm off to change!
ハイタッチ☆メモリー
作詞：ワタナベハジメ　作曲：高尾奏之介
High Touch Memory
Lyrics: Hajime Watanabe / Composition: Sonosuke Takao
いっせーので 君とだけ！
On the count of three, just with you!
もう少し眠りたいけど
I want to sleep a little more, but...
もったいないよ 今日はSunday
It's a waste, today is Sunday
楽しいこと やりたいこと Wake up! 始めようよ
Fun things, things I want to do, wake up! Let's get started
めくりめく季節 君と 次のステージへ
The whirling seasons, with you, to the next stage
声を合わせ 扉開けて 駆け出せ 迷わずに
Unite our voices, open the door, and run out without hesitation
転んでも かっこ悪くてもイイじゃない
Even if we fall, even if we look uncool, that's fine
Stand up! イメージもっと
Stand up! Imagine more
重ねてゆく その先で
Layering them up, beyond that
いっせーので 君とだけ！
On the count of three, just with you!
ハイタッチ 手をたたいて
High touch, clap your hands
奏でるメロディーを
The melody we play...
合図に走り出せ Go!
Run out at the signal, Go!
君となら怖くない
I'm not afraid if I'm with you
ハイタッチ 手と手たたいて
High touch, clap hand to hand
重ねるそのメモリーは
That memory we're building...
明日へのエネルギー Yeah!
Is energy for tomorrow, Yeah!
さあ行こうよ もっと先へ
Come on, let's go further ahead
君となら Happy Lucky Life!
With you, it's a Happy Lucky Life!
（ハピラキラ）
(Happy Lucky)
あの日見た夢の続き
The continuation of the dream I had that day
追いつくその日まで
Until the day I catch up
涙なんて振り切るくらい もっとスピードアップ
Tears, I'll shake them off, and speed up even more
どんな未来になっても 後悔しないよ
No matter what the future holds, I won't regret it
自分自身 選んだ道
The path I chose for myself
踏み出せ迷わずに
Step out without hesitation
落ち込んで　進めなくなった時は
When you're depressed and can't move forward
Wake up! 思い返す
Wake up! Recall
夢見た頃の記憶を
The memories of when you dreamed
手と手で　奏でる　叶える
With hand in hand, we play, we fulfill
煌めく夢を　君とだけ！
A sparkling dream, only with you!
ハイタッチ　その度に
Every time we high-five
繋がっていく心
Our hearts connect
一人じゃないことをそう
That's right, you're not alone
気付かせてくれたよね
You made me realize that
ハイタッチ　手と手叩いて
High-five, clap our hands together
奏でるそのメロディーが
And that melody we play
世界に届くまで Yeah
Until it reaches the world, Yeah
この夢は続いていく
This dream continues
君となら Happy Lucky Live! (ハピラキラ)
With you, Happy Lucky Live! (Hapi Kira)
くじけて歩けない日は
On days when you're discouraged and can't walk
おんぶしてあげる君を
I'll give you a piggyback ride
ほら見てそっちの方が
Look, that way
強く地面　踏み込める
You can step on the ground more firmly
巡り巡る日々を
The cycling days
巡り夢見たステージへ
To the stage I dreamed of
届くその日を見つめて
Gazing at the day it reaches
起こそう　君とだけ！
Let's make it happen, only with you!
手と手を鳴らす度
Every time we clap hands
小さなビッグバン
A small Big Bang
無限のそのチカラを受けて進め！
Receive that infinite power and move forward!
ハイタッチ　手たたいて
High-five, clap your hands
奏でるメロディーを
The melody we play
合図に走り出せ Go!
Start running at the signal, Go!
君とならこわくない
I'm not afraid with you
ハイタッチ　手と手叩いて
High-five, clap our hands together
重ねるそのメモリーは
The memories we stack up
明日へのエネルギー Yeah
Are energy for tomorrow, Yeah
さあ行こうよ　もっと先へ
Let's go even further
君となら Happy Lucky Live! (ハピラキラ)
With you, Happy Lucky Live! (Hapi Kira)
ありがとう！
Thank you!
みんなありがとう！
Thank you everyone!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
あ、みこピー、ありがとう。かわいい。
Ah, Mikopi, thank you. So cute.
ありがとう！
Thank you!
応援してくれているみんなへ
To everyone who supports me,
お〜すごい！
Oh, amazing!
まだまだLIVEの途中ですが！
We're still in the middle of the live, but!
いっぱいおるぜ！
There are so many!
今日はお祝いに来てくれて本当にありがとうございます！
Thank you so much for coming to celebrate today!
にゃっはろー！
Nyahallo!
今日8月1日はデビューして3年目の記念日。
Today, August 1st, is my 3rd anniversary since debut.
おにゃっはろー！
Onyahallo!
去年の今日は休止していてみんなとお祝いが出来なかった。
I was on hiatus on this day last year and couldn't celebrate with everyone.
すごくすごく悔しかったけど…
I was really, really frustrated, but...
にゃっはろー、ありがとう！
Nyahallo, thank you!
後ろもにゃっはろー！
Nyahallo to those in the back too!
今こうして笑顔でみんなに感謝を伝えられるのは
The reason I can express my gratitude to everyone with a smile now
あの時支えてくれたみんななど今まで支えてきてくれたすべてのみんなのおかげです。
is thanks to everyone who supported me back then and all of you who have supported me until now.
にゃっはろー、ありがとう！
Nyahallo, thank you!
ありがとうね。
Thank you.
最高の夏にしよう！
Let's make this the best summer!
そんな気持ちを込めての3周年LIVE、楽しんでもらえてますか？
I hope you're enjoying this 3rd anniversary live filled with those feelings.
たくさんの楽しいことも　悔しいことも　悲しいことも
All the many happy times, frustrating times, and sad times,
うわあ！
Whoa!
一緒にこれからもずっとみんなと一緒に感じていきたい
I want to keep experiencing them together with everyone from now on.
みんなと一緒にこれからもずっと走っていきたい！
I want to keep running together with everyone forever!
みんな、ありがとう！
Everyone, thank you!
これからもみんなにたくさん貰った分笑顔をもっともっと、返せるように
From now on, I want to return even more smiles for all that you've given me.
すごい！いっぱいみんなの顔が見えて。
Amazing! I can see so many of your faces.
4周年目も毎日頑張っていこうと思ってるからこれからも見ててよね！
I plan to work hard every day for my 4th year, so please keep watching me!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
みこと出会ってくれて本当にありがとう。
Thank you so much for meeting Miko.
あ、こっちもありがとう。
Ah, thank you over here too.
みんなのことがだーいだーい大好きだよ！
I love everyone sooo sooo much!
すごい！
Incredible!
みこより
From Miko
はい、ということで！
Alright, so!
じゃじゃーん！中央のステージに来ましたよ。
Ta-da! I've come to the center stage.
みんながいる、すごい！
Everyone's here, amazing!
わぁ〜！
Wow!
うわ〜！
Whoa!
ということでね、あの〜、ここまでたくさん歌ってきましたけど、
So, well, I've sung a lot of songs so far,
なんと残すところ、2曲になります！
And believe it or not, there are only 2 songs left!
みんなね、どうだったかな？
How was it for everyone?
やっぱり夏はね、こう盛り上がったり、ハッピーだったり、するんですけど、
After all, summer is about getting excited and being happy,
今から歌う曲は、こう、みこの、とってもとっても思い出深い曲ですね。
But the next song is a very, very memorable one for Miko.
みこが、初めて生放送をしたときに歌った曲です。
It's the song I sang during my very first live broadcast.
あんときは、めちゃくちゃ泣いちゃって、なんか、なんか、あれだったんだけど、
I cried a lot back then, and it was... well...
今回は、ちゃんと、歌に気持ちを込めて、歌いたいと思います。
This time, I want to sing it properly, putting my heart into it.
それでは、聞いてください。
Now, please listen.
secret base 〜君がくれたもの〜
secret base ~Kimi ga Kureta Mono~
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢 大きな希望 忘れない
10年後の8月 また出会えるのを信じて
The end of summer with you, dreams of the future,
big hopes, I won't forget them.
I believe we'll meet again in August ten years from now.
最高の思い出を…
The best memories...
出会いは ふっとした 瞬間
帰り道の交差点で
声をかけてくれたね 「一緒に帰ろう」
The meeting was a sudden moment,
at the intersection on the way home.
You called out to me, "Let's go home together."
僕は 照れくさそうに カバンで顔を隠しながら
本当は とても とても 嬉しかったよ
Looking embarrassed, hiding my face with my bag,
in truth, I was very, very happy.
あぁ 花火が夜空 きれいに咲いて ちょっとセツナク
あぁ 風が時間とともに 流れる
Ah, the fireworks bloom beautifully in the night sky,
a little bittersweet.
Ah, the wind flows along with time.
嬉しくって 楽しくって 冒険も いろいろしたね
二人の 秘密の 基地の中
So happy, so fun, we went on many adventures,
inside our secret base.
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢 大きな希望 忘れない
10年後の8月 また出会えるのを信じて
The end of summer with you, dreams of the future,
big hopes, I won't forget them.
I believe we'll meet again in August ten years from now.
君が最後まで 心から 「ありがとう」 叫んでたこと
知ってたよ 涙をこらえて 笑顔でさようなら せつないよね
I knew you were shouting "thank you"
from the bottom of your heart until the very end.
Holding back tears, saying goodbye with a smile, it's painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を…
The best memories...
あぁ 夏休みも あと少しで 終わっちゃうから
あぁ 太陽と月 仲良くして
Ah, summer vacation is almost over,
Ah, let the sun and moon get along.
悲しくって 寂しくって 喧嘩も いろいろしたね
二人の 秘密の 基地の中
So sad, so lonely, we had many fights,
inside our secret base.
君が最後まで 心から 「ありがとう」 叫んでたこと
知ってたよ 涙をこらえて 笑顔でさようなら せつないよね
I knew you were shouting "thank you"
from the bottom of your heart until the very end.
Holding back tears, saying goodbye with a smile, it's painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を…
The best memories...
突然の 転校で
Because of a sudden school transfer,
どうしようもなく 手紙 書くよ 電話もするよ
忘れないでね 僕のことを いつまでも 二人の 基地の中
Helpless, I'll write letters, I'll call you,
don't forget me. Always, inside our secret base.
君と夏の終わり ずっと話して 夕日を見てから星を眺め
君の頬を 流れた涙は ずっと忘れない
君が最後まで 大きく手を振ってくれたこと きっと忘れない
だからこうして 夢の中で ずっと永遠に…
The end of summer with you, we talked forever,
watched the sunset and then looked at the stars.
I'll never forget the tears that ran down your cheek.
I surely won't forget that you waved your hand widely until the end.
So like this, in a dream, forever and ever...
君と夏の終わり 将来の夢 大きな希望 忘れない
10年後の8月 また出会えるのを信じて
君が最後まで 心から 「ありがとう」 叫んでたこと
知ってたよ 涙をこらえて 笑顔でさようなら せつないよね
The end of summer with you, dreams of the future,
big hopes, I won't forget them.
I believe we'll meet again in August ten years from now.
I knew you were shouting "thank you"
from the bottom of your heart until the very end.
Holding back tears, saying goodbye with a smile, it's painful, isn't it?
最高の思い出を…
The best memories...
はい、ということで、どうでしたか？みんなありがとう！
Yes, so, how was it? Thank you everyone!
残すところ、2曲となりました。
There are only two songs left.
この曲はですね、
This song is...
まあ、今日みこがね、サプライズもらったんですけど、
Well, today Miko got a surprise,
みこが今度はみんなに、サプライズをしようかなと思います。
And now I'm thinking of giving everyone a surprise.
なんと、みこちゃんの新曲をこちらで発表しようかなと思います。
Believe it or not, I'm going to perform my new song right here.
みなさん聞いてくれますかー？
Will everyone listen to it?
では、
Then,
聞いてください。
please listen.
花月ノ夢。
Kagetsu no Yume.
花月ノ夢
作曲：かんざきひろ
Kagetsu no Yume
Music by Hiro Kanzaki
時代（とき）を越え 今宵も願う
Transcending time, I make a wish tonight as well
途切れぬ想い 届くようにと
So that my unending feelings may reach you
運命（さだめ）だと 気付かないまま
Without realizing it was destiny
貴方の姿を探す
I search for your figure
一夜（ひとよ） 一夜（ひとよ） 追いかける夢
Night after night, a dream I chase
朽ち果ててしまわないように
Lest it should wither away
ひらり ひらり 舞い踊りましょう
Fluttering, fluttering, let's dance together
暁に消えるまでは 口寄せ詠う
Until it vanishes into the dawn, I'll sing a spell
この夢は 儚く揺れる
This dream sways fleetingly
永遠（とわ）に続くように願っても…
Even if I pray for it to last forever...
伝えたい 貴方にだけは
I want to tell you, if only to you
物語の結末を
The conclusion of the story
月夜重ね 辿り着く夢
Accumulated moonlit nights, a dream I finally reach
闇に染まってしまわぬよう
So that I won't be dyed in darkness
桜 桜 咲き誇りましょう
Cherry blossoms, cherry blossoms, let's bloom in full glory
いつか貴方が振り向く その瞬間まで
Until the moment you turn around someday
一夜（ひとよ） 一夜（ひとよ） 語り続けよう
Night after night, let's keep telling the story
幾千の時代（とき）を流れて
Flowing through thousands of eras
ひらり ひらり 舞い踊る夢
Fluttering, fluttering, a dancing dream
今宵 桜の下で Ah 口寄せ詠う
Tonight, under the cherry blossoms, Ah, I sing a spell
はい、ということで、ここからはお知らせの時間です！
Yes, and now, it's time for announcements!
まずは、こちら！さくらみこ活動三周年記念グッズ、エリートな水着の抱き枕カバー！
First up, this! Sakura Miko 3rd Anniversary goods, an elite swimsuit dakimakura cover!
この後22時から販売開始です！
Sales start from 10 PM after this!
こちらのイラストは、ぱん先生に描いていただきましたよ！
This illustration was drawn by Pan-sensei!
とっても可愛いエリートな水着、みんな気に入ってくれたらいいな。
A very cute elite swimsuit, I hope everyone likes it.
裏側は、夏バテをしている...
On the reverse side, she's suffering from summer heat...
うつ伏せになってます。
...is lying face down.
このだらしない顔が、なぜか しっくりきてしまう。
This sloppy face somehow feels just right.
数量限定バージョンには、特典として直筆サイン入りポストカードがついてきます。
The limited quantity version comes with a hand-signed postcard as a bonus.
今回は前回の倍、いや、それ以上、またもや監禁されながら書かせていただきますよ！
This time, I'll be writing twice as many as last time, no, even more, while being confined again!
そして通常バージョン特典には、箔押しのサイン入りポストカードがついてきます。
And the standard version bonus includes a foil-stamped signed postcard.
お次はこちら！
Next is this!
7月29日から秋葉原にあるステラマップカフェさんにて、
From July 29th, at STELLAMAP Cafe in Akihabara,
コラボカフェを8月15日まで期間限定で開催中です。
...the collab cafe is being held for a limited time until Aug 15th.
こちらのコラボカフェ限定グッズをBOOTHにて販売中！
These collaboration cafe exclusive goods are now on sale at BOOTH!
メインビジュアルはOrdan先生に、ちびキャライラストはトダ先生に描いていただきました。
The main visual was drawn by Ordan-sensei, and the chibi character illustrations by Toda-sensei.
とってもかわいい！
They're so cute!
コラボカフェに来れないよ～って方も、BOOTHで大丈夫！
Even if you can't come to the collab cafe, you can get them on BOOTH!
ぜひ記念にコラボカフェグッズ、ゲットしてね！
Please get the collab cafe goods to commemorate the occasion!
そしてなんと！こいつがエリートカフェに居座るみたいです。
And surprisingly! This guy seems to be taking up residence at the Elite Cafe.
みこの1日店長の日には、動き出すかも…？！
On the day Miko is the store manager for a day, it might start moving...?!
これは現地みこぴーのつぶやきをチェックするしかない！
You'll just have to check the tweets from the local Mikopis!
あ、ちなみに店内は撮影OKです。
Oh, by the way, photography is allowed inside the cafe.
でもみんなの顔は隠してくださいね。
But please hide everyone's faces.
コラボカフェの詳細やグッズの購入ページは、
Details about the collab cafe and the purchase page...
概要欄に記載してあると思うので、ぜひチェック！
...should be in the description, so please check it out!
そしてこの後すぐ、メンバー限定放送を予定しているので、
And right after this, a member-only broadcast is scheduled...
ぜひこの機会に、さくらみこのメンバー加入、待ってるぜー！
...so I'll be waiting for you to join Sakura Miko's membership at this opportunity!
以上、エリート巫女アイドル、さくらみこでした！
That's all from the Elite Miko Idol, Sakura Miko!
4年目も頑張るぞー、おー！
I'll do my best in my fourth year! Yeah!
みんな付いてきてね！
Everyone, please keep following me!